

# Felipe Sales

Software Developer







sales.felipeb@gmail.com

## Skills

#### Tech

- Web Dev
- Algorithms
- UX
- Scrum
- Databases
- Distributed Systems
- Data Analysis

#### Personal

- Organization
- Team Work
- Creativity
- Entrepreneurship
- Commitment

# Languages

- Portuguese (native)
- English (fluent)
- French (intermediate)

### #Leadership

Leader of a global software development team project about Realtor Website, where half of the team was located in Florida USA, during the class of Software Engineering at SFSU Fall 2014. The software was developed from scratch and including collecting the requirements through development and QA tests.

Leader of software development team project that was developed by the computer science department UFCG. It is used by our graduates to evaluate professors.

### #Experience

Tutorial Education University Program (PET)

2012 - 2014

- Main Activities:
  - Academic Research
  - Journal News Writer
  - Events Organization
  - Web Dev

Distributed Systems Laboratory (LSD)

2015 - 2016

- Main Activities:
  - Academic Research
  - App Development
  - UX Studies

Software Practices Laboratory (SPLab)

Junior Developer

2016 - Present

Main Activities: Frontend/Backend Development

**Technologies**: .Net MVC5, React Js, SqlServer, Azure, Razor, .Net WebApi, Azure

Severino Cabral Municipal Theatre

Zouk Dance Instructor

2016 - 2017

#### #Education

Federal University of Campina Grande (UFCG)

Bachelor of Computer Science 2012 - 2017

San Francisco State University (SFSU)

Bachelor of Computer Science 2014 - 2015

### **#Technologies**

**Programming Languages: C#**, Java, JavaScript, R, Python, CSS, HTML

**Frameworks:** BootsTrap, AngularJs(1.0), Ionic, D3Js, .**NET**,

**Platforms:** Windows, Linux, Mac, **Azure**, AWS, Heroku **Technologies: Git**, MongoDb, OracleDb, Firebase, **SQLServer**.

React Js, Flask, NodeJs, Less, Semantic UI, MVC5.